

Contacts

Contacts: <u>+380974335970</u>

Email: rudomanovdmitrij@gmail.com

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/

GIT: https://github.com/

Tech Skills

- HTML5
- CSS3
- دردد
- GIT
- JavaScript
- WebPack
- React
- Redux

Soft Skills

- Communication
- Teamwork
- Decision-making
- Leadership
- Creativity
- Stress management

Language Skills

- Russian : NATIVE
- Ukrainian : NATIVE
- English: Upper-intermediate

Front-End Developer

Dmitrij Rudomanov

I'm a Frontend developer with experience in building websites and APP`s. Whether you're trying to win work, list your services or even create a whole online store – I can help! I'm experienced in HTML and CSS3, SCSS, JS and React. Regular communication is really important to me, so let's keep in touch!

Projects

1.	'PHONEBOOK' web-app
2.	'FILMOTEKA' web-site [HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, JavaScript]
3.	<u>'WebStudio' web-site</u>
4.	'ICECREAM' web-site
5.	'WOODER' web-site [HTML5, CSS3, SCSS]
6.	'OFDR' Insurance web-site
7.	'FUNIRO' web-store
8.	'LOGO' sport web-store
9.	'BENTLEY' web-site
LO.	'BINARY' web-site [HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, JavaScript]
L 1.	'Prime-One' web-site
L2.	'BIKE' web-site

Work Experience

Waiter Restaurant 'SHO PO CHEM'

June 2019 - September 2019 | Country Ukraine

- Taking orders from visitors
- Customer service

Web-site editor Svet-LED Company

September 2019 - January 2019 | Country Ukraine

- Editing the list of products on the site
- Products information update

Education

PSACEA

International Economics and business

September 2018 - June 2023 | Country Ukraine

Additional Education

GOIT

FULL STACK course online

August 2021 - June 2022 | Country Ukraine